Caspar Wistar Papers 1794-1893 1794-1817 Mss.B.W76
American Philosophical Society
- Letters to Caspar Wistar, 1794-1893; 1.0 vol. (Volume 1)
  - Report of committee on paper on bones by Caspar Wistar, March 3, 1815; 9-3/4x7-1/2; American Philosophical Society
    D.S.: Thos. T.Hewson and John Syng Dorsey. 2p.,end. (See Letters to C.Wistar, no. 42.) Cf. Minutes, p.452.
  - Report of committee on paper on fossils by Caspar Wistar, Jan. 19, 1816; 9-3/4x6-3/4; American Philosophical Society
    D.S.: J. Corrèa de Serra, Zaccheus Collins and James Mease. 1p.and end. (See Letters to Caspar Wistar, no. 43.) Cf. Minutes, p.460.
  - Engraving of Caspar Wistar., 43a.
  - Letter to Mrs. Eliza[beth Mifflin] Wistar, July 22, 1830; 10x8; American Philosophical Society
    Philadelphia, A.L.S.: Peter S. DuPonceau. 1p.and add.,end. Seal. (see Letters to C.Wistar, no. 44.) Asks to borrow portrait of C.Wistar and have Sully copy it.